Dale Wilson

Adjunct Professor at University of the Sciences in Philadelphia

Lansdale, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Dale-Wilson/1f74c261bd8dde97

PharmD with more than 15 years' experience in retail, clinical, and hospital settings, plus home infusion and mail order. Interface regularly with manufacturers and wholesalers to ensure well-being of patients. Major areas of expertise include:

- * Pharmacy rules and regulations * Employee recruiting and training
- * Drug recalls * Introduction of new products
- * Schedule II procedures and protocols * Emergency procedures
- * Patient compliance programs * Public presentations

Registered Pharmacist in Commonwealth of Pennsylvania

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pharmacist

Neff Pharmacy Management - Philadelphia, PA - 2008 to Present

- * Fill and review prescriptions for accuracy of medication, strength, frequency, and directions.
- * Maintain current and proper inventory levels including removing outdated merchandise, preparing returns, receiving, and stocking.

Pharmacist

PharmPro Management Association - Plymouth Meeting, PA - 2004 to 2007

- * Coordinated delivery to nurses and/or patients for time sensitive medication administration.
- * Calculated, mixed and checked weekly medication delivery of antibiotics, chemotherapy, TPN and biologicals for patients.
- * Prepared and/or sterilized medication forms; distributed, controlled, inspected, stored, labeled and maintained records.

Pharmacist

General Healthcare Resources - Plymouth Meeting, PA - 2002 to 2007

- * Fulfilled various assignments at Neighbor Care Pharmacy and City of Philadelphia Health Care Centers.
- * Communicated with patients, physicians, insurance companies, Medicare, and Medicaid to ensure proper drug therapy for each patient.

Pharmacist

PharmPro Management Association - Brookhaven, PA - 1999 to 2007

* Dispensed up to approximately 1200-1500 prescriptions per week at various pharmacies as assigned.

EDUCATION

University of the Sciences in Philadelphia - Philadelphia, PA 2002 to 2007

Bachelor of Science

Philadelphia College of Pharmacy and Science - Philadelphia, PA 1988 to 1993